(light upbeat guitar music)
♪ Feeling my way through the darkness ♪
♪ Guided by a beating heart ♪
♪ I can't tell where
the journey will end ♪
♪ But I know where to start ♪
♪ They tell me I'm too
young to understand ♪
♪ They say I'm caught up in a dream ♪
♪ Well life will pass me by
if I don't open up my eyes ♪
♪ Well that's fine by me ♪
♪ So wake me up when it's all over ♪
♪ When I'm wiser and I'm older ♪
♪ All this time I was
finding myself, and I ♪
♪ Didn't know I was lost ♪
♪ So wake me up when it's all over ♪
♪ When I'm wiser and I'm older ♪
♪ All this time I was
finding myself, and I ♪
♪ Didn't know I was lost ♪
- The others, they don't like us.
- Yeah, I know.
- Why?
(light upbeat music)
(energetic upbeat music)
(energetic upbeat music continues)
♪ I tried carrying the
weight of the world ♪
♪ But I only have two hands ♪
♪ Hope I get the chance
to travel the world ♪
♪ But I don't have any plans ♪
♪ Wish that I could stay
forever this young ♪
♪ Not afraid to close my eyes ♪
♪ Life's a game made for everyone ♪
♪ And love is a prize ♪
♪ So wake me up when it's all over ♪
♪ When I'm wiser and I'm older ♪
♪ All this time I was
finding myself, and I ♪
♪ Didn't know I was lost ♪
♪ So wake me up when it's all over ♪
♪ When I'm wiser and I'm older ♪
♪ All this time I was
finding myself, and I ♪
♪ I didn't know I was lost ♪
♪ I didn't know ♪
(door thuds)
- Get up! Pack you things.
- Where are we going?
- Somewhere we belong.
(energetic upbeat music)
(energetic upbeat music continues)
(birds chirping)
(footsteps tapping)
(wind swooshing)
(energetic upbeat music)